# ROMJAN

romjanbepari727@gmail.com | +971527807057 | DHAKA, Bangladesh 8040

## WEBSITE, PORTFOLIO, PROFILES

- https://romjan123.github.io/romjan/
- https://twitter.com/romjan1995
- https://linkedin.com/in/romjan1995

### **PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY**

Organized and efficient Data Entry Clerk with 2 years of experience in data organization, proofreading and word processing. Multi-talented in smoothly handling office administration support tasks. Team player works to support group efforts to meet critical deadlines.

### **SKILLS**

- HTML
- CSS
- Data Entry
- MS Office

- Written Communication
- Attention to Detail
- Decision-Making

### **WORK HISTORY**

Feb 2021 - Current

### **Data Entry Clerk**

Ayesha Ismaeil Technical Services - Dubai, AE

- Completed data entry tasks with accuracy and efficiency.
- Scanned documents and saved in database to keep records of essential organizational information.
- Entered numerical data into databases with speed and accuracy using 10-key pad.
- Organized, sorted and checked input data against original documents.
- Located and corrected data entry errors and reported to management.
- Advanced sales cycle plans by maximizing placement of promotions, point of sale materials and product visibility.
- Planned and coordinated product availability for advertising and promotion purposes.

Jul 2017 - Jul 2019 **Sales Merchandiser** Arabian Trading Supplier -Riyadh, KSA

- Ran markdown reports, managed store replenishment and analyzed buying reports.
- Updated pricing and signage to complete product displays and educate customers.
- Inspected merchandise for quality and arranged proper display location on floor.
- Answered customer questions regarding store merchandise, department information and pricing.

### **EDUCATION**

Jul 2019

**Under Graduate:** Accounting

National University of Bangladesh | Dhaka

- Continuing education in Accounting
- Compete BBA 2nd Semester out of 4 semester in 2019

Jul 2015

# **High School Diploma**

Purbo Madaripur College | Dhaka

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

• Certified Data Entry Clerk, Ayesha Ismaeil Technical Services - 2021-2022

### **FOOTBALL**

I play football because **it is fun, challenging and exciting**. Most of people love being part of a team. Football teaches cooperation and team work, helps develop positive social skills and teaches respect for others. It helps build self-confidence, a positive self-image and self-worth.

# English Upper intermediate (B2) Arabic Elementary (A2)